Guide to the H. Boone Porter Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Course Materials, 1947-1996; Series V
  - Courses taught
    - General Theological Seminary: Liturgics 22: "Contemporary Parish", 1963, 1965, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 231-233)
    - General Theological Seminary: Liturgics 23: "Divine Office", 1962, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 234-235)
    - General Theological Seminary: Liturgics 25: "Occasional Offices", 1964 (Box 27, Folder 236)
    - General Theological Seminary: Liturgics 29: "Pastoral Theology", 1966 (Box 27, Folder 237)
    - General Theological Seminary: Liturgics 30: "Theology of the Sacraments", 1969 (Box 27, Folder 238)
    - General Theological Seminary: Liturgics 101: "Anglican Liturgics", 1961-1962, 1964, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 239-241)
    - General Theological Seminary: Liturgics 102: "Latin Liturgies", 1962, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 242-243)
    - General Theological Seminary: Liturgics 104: "Liturgies of Spain", 1963 (Box 28, Folder 244)
    - General Theological Seminary: Liturgics 104: "Liturgies of Spain", 1967, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 245-246)
    - General Theological Seminary: Liturgics 106: "Northern Italian Rites", 1964, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 247-248)
    - General Theological Seminary: Liturgics 112: "Anglican Liturgy", 1960, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 249-250)
    - General Theological Seminary: History 40: "History of Religions", 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 251-252)
    - General Theological Seminary: Polity 133, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 253)
    - General Theological Seminary: reference materials, 1960-1970 (Box 29, Folder 254)
    - General Theological Seminary: degree examinations, 1960-1970 (Box 29, Folder 255)
    - General Theological Seminary: dissertation review, 1968, 1970, 1982, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 256-259)
    - Notre Dame University: Liturgics 560: "Ecumenical Trends in Worship", 1975 (Box 30, Folder 260)
    - Yale Divinity School: REL 790A: "The Book of Common Prayer", 1996 (Box 30, Folder 261-262)
- Major Organizations Served, 1954-2003; Series VI
  - Associated Parishes
    - General files, 1958-1968 (Box 30, Folder 263-273)
    - General files, 1969-1989 (Box 31, Folder 274-289)
    - General files, 1990-1997 (Box 32, Folder 290-297)
    - AP publications: miscellaneous, 1954-1978 (Box 32, Folder 298-299)
    - AP publications: "Issues", 1970-1976 (Box 33, Folder 300)
    - AP publications: "OPEN", 1993-1995 (Box 33, Folder 301)
    - AP publications: "Shares", 1958-1962 (Box 33, Folder 302)
    - Educational materials, 1956-1998 (Box 33, Folder 303-305)
    - HBP publishing, 1965-1968 (Box 33, Folder 306)
    - 1965 NY Liturgical Conference: organization, correspondence, papers given, publicity, accommodations, etc. (Box 33, Folder 307-316)
    - 1999 Conference Committee: conference site selection, meeting information, correspondence, etc., 1996-1999 (Box 34, Folder 317-324)
    - 1999 Conference Committee: correspondence: HBP's OPEN article, Roland Allen book, correspondence with Charleston, Crapson, Guilford, Harris, Hassell, Jelinek, J. Kelsey, S. Kelsey, Mercado, Miller, Morris, Putnam, Ray, Snyder, Tombaugh, Wilson, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 325-342)
    - 1999 Conference Committee: correspondence: miscellaneous, sponsorship, financial records, 1997-1999 (Box 36, Folder 343-353)
    - 1999 Conference Committee: financial records, 1997-2000 (Box 37, Folder 354-359)
  - Episcopal Literature Fund, Inc./H. Boone and Violet M. Porter Charitable Foundation
    - Administrative records: correspondence, 1981-1989 (Box 37, Folder 360)
    - Administrative records: official papers, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 361)
    - Administrative records: gifts, 1982-2003 (Box 37, Folder 362)
    - Administrative records: gifts: St. George's College, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 363)
    - Administrative records: gifts: Presiding Bishop's Fund, 1988-1990 (Box 37, Folder 364)
    - Administrative records: Board meetings, 1982-1991 (Box 37, Folder 365)
    - Financial records, 1981-1991 (Box 38, Folder 366-370)
    - Jerusalem Interim: correspondence: Peterson, Schaitberg, St. George's College, miscellaneious, 1989-1996 (Box 38, Folder 371-375)
    - Jerusalem Interim: promotional information, 1990-1996 (Box 39, Folder 376)
    - Jerusalem Interim: students, 1992-1996 (Box 39, Folder 377-386)
      For photographs of students participating in the Jerusalem Interim, see Series X, box 83, folder 860.
  - New Directions/Leadership Academy for New Directions/Roanridge
    - ND/LAND administrative records, 1972-1974 (Box 39, Folder 387-390)
    - ND/LAND administrative records: consultants, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 391)
    - ND/LAND administrative records: Bishop Gordon, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 392)
    - ND/LAND administrative records: Bishop's Conference, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 393)
    - ND/LAND administrative records: Joint Strategy and Action Committee, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 394)
    - ND/LAND administrative records, 1975-1977 (Box 40, Folder 395-398)
    - ND/LAND administrative records, LAND packets, 1978-1980 (Box 41, Folder 399-404)
    - ND/LAND administrative records, LAND packets, 1981-1999 (Box 42, Folder 405-412)
    - 1975 LAND at Roanridge: faculty (Box 42, Folder 413)
      For photographs of the 1975-1977 LAND sessions at Roanridge, see Series X, box 83, folders 857-858, and for an audio history of Kansas LAND, see Series X, box 84, folder 865.
    - 1975 LAND at Roanridge: participant reports (Box 42, Folder 414)
    - 1975 LAND at Roanridge: student reviews (Box 43, Folder 415)
    - 1975 LAND at Roanridge: miscellaneous applications, etc. (Box 43, Folder 416)
    - 1975 LAND at Roanridge: Brown, David; Cuthbertson, Hugh; Dunne, Joseph; Gravely, Herbert; Greene, Robert; Hopkins, Harold; Lewis, William; Logan, William; Martin, James; McDougall, Robert; Moser, Paul Henry; Pilling, J. T.; Rivers, John; Rockwood, Brad (Box 43, Folder 417-430)
    - 1975 LAND at Roanridge: Schaitburger, Stephen; White, Roger; Wright, William (Box 44, Folder 431-433)
    - 1976 LAND at Roanridge: miscellaneous information (Box 44, Folder 434)
    - 1976 LAND at Roanridge: faculty (Box 44, Folder 435)
    - 1976 LAND at Roanridge: mentors; participant questionnaires, application requests, miscellaneous correspondence (Box 44, Folder 436-439)
    - 1976 LAND at Roanridge: Burton, Bob; Gracie, Thomas; Hay, LaMar; Jackson, Thomas;James, Paul; Kerr, Joseph; King, Kale; Leather, Robert; Maxwell, Robert; McIllmurray, John; Neeley, Harry; Parmeter, George; Scott, Benjamin (Box 44, Folder 440-452)
    - 1976 LAND at Roanridge: Sedgwick, Stephen; Smith, Ronald; Stanway, David; Stivers, Alton; Tachau, Charles; Titus, Luke; Tomalin, W. Patrick; Tripp, Arthur; Willing, Robert (Box 45, Folder 453-461)
    - 1977 LAND at Roanridge: miscellaneous; mentors; correspondence (Box 45, Folder 462-465)
    - 1977 LAND at Roanridge: Apple, F. Charles; Brake, William; Brown, Allen; Chang, Richard Sui On; Crim, B. Shepard; Day, Charles; Gordon, Robert; McLennan, Robert; McInnis, William (Box 45, Folder 466-474)
    - 1977 LAND at Roanridge: Monk, Arthur; Peters, Albert; Rudd, Neilson; Schane, Clifford; Simons, Webster; Sisk, Mark; Tonks, Basil (Box 46, Folder 475-481)
    - LAND programmatic materials: Theological Education by Extension, 1975-1977 (Box 46, Folder 482)
    - LAND programmatic materials: clergy contracts; stewardship information; grouping of parishes; survey instruments, 1975-1977 (Box 46, Folder 483-486)
    - Publicity and promotions, 1974-1977 (Box 46, Folder 487-492)
    - Publicity and promotions: ND/LAND brochures, Roanridge brochures, 1970-1977 (Box 47, Folder 493-494)
    - "Diocesan Theological Training" information, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 495-496)
    - Collected materials: "Town and Country"; Archdeacon conference; book information; Lowery "Small Church" essay; food programs; White's "Celebration of Smallness" pamphlet; Dudley "Small Church" essay; ecology, 1960-1977, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 497-504)
    - Collected materials: Roanridge maps, no date (Box 47, Folder 505)
    - Collected materials: ND publications, 1970-1977 (Box 47, Folder 506)
    - Collected materials: Church leadership, 1970-1977 (Box 48, Folder 507)
    - Collected materials: order forms, 1970-1977 (Box 48, Folder 508)
    - Roanridge administrative records: personnel records, 1973-1976 (Box 48, Folder 509)
    - Roanridge administrative records: terms of employment, 1970-1977 (Box 48, Folder 510)
    - Roanridge administrative records: correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 48, Folder 511)
    - Roanridge administrative records: audio-visual library, no date (Box 48, Folder 512)
    - Roanridge administrative records: Episcopal Church amendment, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 513)
    - Roanridge administrative records: Freilich Study, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 514)
    - Roanridge administrative records: West Missouri Training Program, 1970-1971 (Box 48, Folder 515)
    - Roanridge finances and governance: Cochel Last Will and Testament, 1944 (Box 48, Folder 516)
    - Roanridge finances and governance: Tiffany Fellowship, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 517)
    - Roanridge finances and governance: property and rentals, 1949-1976 (Box 48, Folder 518)
    - Roanridge finances and governance, 1970-1971 (Box 48, Folder 519-520)
    - Roanridge finances and governance, HPB report (1974), 1972-1975 (Box 49, Folder 521-525)
    - Roanridge finances and governance, 1976-1977 (Box 50, Folder 526-527)
    - Roanridge conferences: Non-metropolitan; Non-Indian; Special Ministry Preparation; General Ordination Exam reading, 1971-1976 (Box 50, Folder 528-531)
    - Roanridge instructional Church services: Holy Week and Easter; Advent, Christmas, Epiphany; Easter Vigil; "Church in Summer"; Holy Week, 1970-1972 (Box 50, Folder 532-536)
    - Roanridge instructional Church services: Easter Vigil; Green Day; Easter Vigil; "Big Day in Lent"; Easter Vigil; "Lift in Lent"; miscellaneous, 1972-1976 (Box 51, Folder 537-546)
  - Roland Allen Forum
    - Conference planning: Pacific Basin Conference (Hawaii), 1983 (Box 51, Folder 547-549)
    - Conference planning, 1984-1985 (Box 51, Folder 550-551)
    - Conference planning, 1986-1999 (Box 52, Folder 552-564)
    - Research materials: Allen family correspondence, 1963-1995 (Box 52, Folder 565)
      For related photographs, see Series X, box 83, folder 862.
    - Research materials: biographical research, no date (Box 53, Folder 566-567)
    - HBP articles and essays, 1975-1988 (Box 53, Folder 568)
  - Standing Liturgical Commission
    - General records, 1966-1977 (Box 53, Folder 569-572)
    - Ordination Rites committees, 1967-1968 (Box 54, Folder 573)
    - Ordination Rites committees: consultants' reactions to drafts of Ordination Rites, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 574)
    - Ordination Rites committees: draft of HBP's introduction to Rites, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 575)
    - Ordination Rites committees: ecumenical research, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 576)
    - Ordination Rites committees: drafts of Ordination Rites, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 577)
    - Ordination Rites committees: drafts of Bishop Ordination Rites, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 578)
    - Ordination Rites committees, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 579)
    - Ordination Rites committees: consultants' reactions to drafts of Ordination Rites, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 580)
    - Ordination Rites committees, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 581)
    - Ordination Rites committees: consultants' reactions to drafts of Ordination Rites, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 582)
    - Ordination Rites committees, 1971-1972 (Box 55, Folder 583-585)
    - Ordination Rites committees: consultants' reactions to drafts of Ordination Rites, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 586)
    - Ordination Rites committees, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 587)
    - Ordination Rites committees: "Services for Trial Use", 1973 (Box 55, Folder 588)
    - Ordination Rites committees, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 589)
    - Ordination Rites committees: Bishops' reactions to drafts of Ordination Rites, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 590)
    - Ordination Rites committees: other reactions to drafts of Ordination Rites, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 591)
    - Ordination Rites committees: "Services for Trial Use", 1974 (Box 56, Folder 592)
    - Ordination Rites committees: Ordinal draft, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 593)
    - Ordination Rites committees, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 594)
    - Ordination Rites committees: "Services for Trial Use", 1975-1977 (Box 56, Folder 595)
    - Ordination Rites committees: distributional materials, 1967-1977 (Box 56, Folder 596)
    - Other committees served: Committee on the Holy Eucharist, 1970-1975 (Box 57, Folder 597)
    - Other committees served: Committee on Canons, 1971-1974 (Box 57, Folder 598)
    - Other committees served: Committee on Doctrine and Worship, 1972-1973 (Box 57, Folder 599)
    - Other committees served: Committee on the Daily Office, 1972-1978 (Box 57, Folder 600-604)
    - Other committees served: Committee on the Church Year, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 605)
    - Other committees served: Committee on the Church Year, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 606-608)
    - Other committees served: Theology Committee, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 609)
    - Other committees served: Legislative Committee, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 610)
    - Miscellaneous revisions and proposals: lectionaries, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 611)
    - Miscellaneous revisions and proposals: "Blessing of a Church", 1972-1973 (Box 58, Folder 612-613)
    - Miscellaneous revisions and proposals: "Celebration of a New Ministry", 1973 (Box 58, Folder 614)
    - Miscellaneous revisions and proposals: new optional Evensong, 1972-1975 (Box 59, Folder 615-618)
    - Miscellaneous revisions and proposals: various new Propers, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 619)
    - Miscellaneous revisions and proposals: re. filioque clause, 1974-1975, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 620-621)
    - Miscellaneous revisions and proposals: marriage and burial, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 622)
    - Miscellaneous revisions and proposals: Epiphany Cana theme, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 623)
    - HBP's initiatives: Armed Forces Prayer Book, 1966-1969 (Box 59, Folder 624)
    - HBP's initiatives: re.blessing "things", 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 625)
    - HBP's initiatives: article: "Meaning of New Liturgy", 1967 (Box 60, Folder 626)
    - HBP's initiatives: Prayer Book Studies 20, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 627)
    - HBP's initiatives: Prayer Book revision defense, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 628)
    - HBP's initiatives: "Reproaches", 1976 (Box 60, Folder 629)
    - HBP's initiatives: Self-Supporting Ministry, 1963-1967 (Box 60, Folder 630)
    - HBP's initiatives: Self-Supporting Ministry: foreign mission, 1963 (Box 60, Folder 631)
    - HBP's initiatives: Self-Supporting Ministry: canonical change, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 632)
    - HBP's initiatives: Self-Supporting Ministry: Seabury Conference, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 633)
    - HBP's initiatives: Self-Supporting Ministry: Ridley Consultation, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 634)
    - HBP's initiatives: Self-Supporting Ministry, 1965-1968 (Box 60, Folder 635)
    - HBP's initiatives: Self-Supporting Ministry: conference, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 636)
    - HBP's initiatives: Self-Supporting Ministry, 1969-1972 (Box 60, Folder 637)
    - HBP's initiatives: Self-Supporting Ministry: "Multiplying the Ministry of Christ", 1970 (Box 61, Folder 638)
    - HBP's initiatives: Self-Supporting Ministry: conference, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 639)
    - HBP's initiatives: Self-Supporting Ministry, 1971-1972 (Box 61, Folder 640)
    - HBP's initiatives: Self-Supporting Ministry: HBP's reports, 1970s-1980s (Box 61, Folder 641)
    - HBP's initiatives: Self-Supporting Ministry: NON-STOP, 1971-1972 (Box 61, Folder 642)
    - HBP's initiatives: Self-Supporting Ministry: promotional materials, 1970s (Box 61, Folder 643)
    - HBP's initiatives: Self-Supporting Ministry: miscellaneous materials, no date (Box 61, Folder 644)
- Other Organizations Served, 1963-1999; Series VII
  - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks
    - General records, 1973-1980, 1991-1996 (Box 62, Folder 645-652)
    - Conferences, 1973-1976, 1993-1996 (Box 62, Folder 653-660)
  - Alcuin Club
    - Correspondence: complaints, 1973-1975 (Box 63, Folder 661)
    - Correspondence: inquiries, 1971-1977 (Box 63, Folder 662)
    - Correspondence: libraries, 1972-1977 (Box 63, Folder 663)
    - Correspondence: miscellaneous, 1975-1987 (Box 63, Folder 664)
    - Membership records: alphabetical-numerical index, 1970-1977 (Box 63, Folder 665)
    - Membership records: numerical:, 1970-1977 (Box 63, Folder 666-668)
    - Membership records: non-numerical, 1970-1977 (Box 63, Folder 669)
    - Publicity, 1975-1976 (Box 63, Folder 670)
    - Reports, 1969-1983 (Box 63, Folder 671)
    - Re. reviewing books, 1970-1977 (Box 64, Folder 672)
    - Financial records: billing information: dues received, 1974-1977 (Box 64, Folder 673-676)
    - Official stamps, no date (Box 64, Folder 677)
  - American Society of Church History
    - General records, 1981-1983 (Box 64, Folder 678)
  - Anglican Consultation on Church Authority
    - General records, 1989-1995 (Box 64, Folder 679)
  - Anglican Consultative Council
    - Correspondence, 1963-1977 (Box 64, Folder 680)
    - General mailings, 1972-1976 (Box 64, Folder 681)
  - Anglican Liturgical Consultation
    - General records, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 682)
  - Anglican Society
    - Correspondence, 1978-1999 (Box 65, Folder 683-684)
    - Advertising with The Living Church, 1979-1991 (Box 65, Folder 685)
    - HBP's reviews and articles, 1983-1998 (Box 65, Folder 686)
  - Anglican Theological Review
    - Administrative records, 1965 (Box 65, Folder 687)
    - HBP's book reviews, 1970-1979 (Box 65, Folder 688-690)
    - Executive Board records, 1985-1998 (Box 65, Folder 691-693)
  - Appalachian People's Service Organization
    - General records, 1972-1975 (Box 66, Folder 694)
  - Association of Diocesan Worship Commissions
    - General records, 1977-1983 (Box 66, Folder 695)
  - Coalition 14
    - Executive Board records, 1971-1974 (Box 66, Folder 696)
  - Conference of Diocesan Executives
    - Executive Board records, 1971-1977 (Box 66, Folder 697)
  - Consultation on Church Union
    - General records, 1968-1973 (Box 67, Folder 698-701)
    - Worship Committee records, 1970-1973 (Box 67, Folder 702-705)
    - Re. Baptism, 1970-1972 (Box 67, Folder 706)
    - Re. Eucharist, 1967-1973 (Box 67, Folder 707)
    - Re. Ordination, 1969-1970 (Box 68, Folder 708)
  - Consultation on Common Texts
    - General records, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 709)
  - Division of Christian Life and Mission
    - General records, 1967-1969 (Box 68, Folder 710)
  - Ecumenical and Interfaith Relations Office
    - General records, 1994-1997 (Box 68, Folder 711)
  - Episcopal Church Missionary Community
    - General records, 1974-1977 (Box 68, Folder 712)
  - Episcopalian Radio-TV Foundation
    - Correspondence and general mailings, 1975-1976 (Box 68, Folder 713)
  - Episcopalians United
    - General records, 1992-1994 (Box 68, Folder 714)
  - Executive Council of the Episcopal Church
    - General records, 1974-1977 (Box 68, Folder 715)
  - Fellowship of Saints Alban and Sergius
    - General records, 1990-1993 (Box 68, Folder 716)
  - Forward Movement
    - Correspondence, 1991-1996 (Box 68, Folder 717)
    - HBP's "Day by Day" contribution, 1992-1993 (Box 68, Folder 718)
  - Governing Board of Examining Chaplains
    - Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 68, Folder 719)
  - General Board of Examining Chaplains
    - Meetings records, 1974-1976 (Box 68, Folder 720)
    - General Ordination Exams, 1972-1977 (Box 69, Folder 721)
  - Home Department
    - Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 69, Folder 722)
    - HBP's reports, 1967-1968 (Box 69, Folder 723)
  - International Commission on English in the Liturgy
    - General records, 1967-1977 (Box 69, Folder 724)
  - Joint Commission on Church Music
    - General records, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 725)
  - Joint Committee for Non-Metropolitan Areas
    - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 69, Folder 726)
    - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 727)
  - Joint Strategy and Action Committee
    - General records, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 728)
  - Mid-America Regional Council
    - General records, 1976-1977 (Box 70, Folder 729)
  - National Association of Self-Supporting Active Ministry
    - General records, 1973-1990 (Box 70, Folder 730-731)
  - National Center for the Diaconate
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 70, Folder 732)
  - Non-Metropolitan Issues Group
    - General records, 1971-1977 (Box 70, Folder 733)
  - North American Academy of Liturgy
    - General records, 1980-1991 (Box 70, Folder 734-735)
    - General records, 1991-1999 (Box 71, Folder 736-737)
    - Editorial Committee records, 1987-1989 (Box 71, Folder 738)
    - Ministry and Orders Group, 1976 (Box 71, Folder 739)
    - Financial: HBP's dues, 1983-1992 (Box 71, Folder 740)
  - North American Association for the Diaconate
    - Correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 71, Folder 741)
  - Partners Making a Difference
    - General records, 1991-1993 (Box 71, Folder 742)
    - HBP's press reports, 1991-1996 (Box 71, Folder 743)
  - Rural Workers Fellowship
    - General records, 1970-1977 (Box 71, Folder 744)
    - Administrative correspondence, 1970-1977 (Box 71, Folder 745)
  - Societas Liturgica
    - Conferences: Washington, D.C., 1979 (Box 72, Folder 746)
    - Conferences: Brixen, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 747)
    - Conferences: Toronto, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 748)
    - Conferences: Dublin, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 749)
    - Conferences: Dublin: papers, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 750)
    - Conferences: Finland, 1997 (Box 72, Folder 751)
    - Conferences: miscellaneous (not attended by HBP), 1978-1987 (Box 72, Folder 752)
    - Financial: HBP's dues, 1978-1991 (Box 72, Folder 753)
    - Miscellaneous general records, 1979-1982 (Box 72, Folder 754)
  - The Living Church
    - Correspondence: Board, 1990-1999 (Box 73, Folder 755)
    - Correspondence: editorial, 1973-1998 (Box 73, Folder 756)
      See also HBP's correspondence relating to the "C.S. Lewis Hoax" in Series I, box 6, folders 45-47.
    - HBP's articles, 1993-1999 (Box 73, Folder 757-758)
    - Financial records, 1985-1987 (Box 73, Folder 759)
      See also information on the joint advertising agreement with the Anglican Society in Series VII, box 65, folder 685.
  - West Kentucky Ministry Program
    - General records, 1970-1976 (Box 73, Folder 760)
  - Diocesan work
    - Cuttyhunk Church, 1968-1986 (Box 73, Folder 761)
    - Diocese of Connecticut, 1991-1998 (Box 74, Folder 762)
    - Diocese of Kentucky, 1971-1974 (Box 74, Folder 763)
    - Diocese of Milwaukee, 1973-1999 (Box 74, Folder 764)
- Collected Materials, 1957-1995; Series VIII
  - Eucharist: service guides, 1970s (Box 74, Folder 765)
  - Eucharist: Galley book, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 766)
  - Hymnals: proposed texts, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 767)
  - Hymnals: "The Liturgical Coordinator", 1984 (Box 75, Folder 768)
  - Hymnals: "Episcopal Musician's Handbook", 1996 (Box 75, Folder 769)
  - 21 issues of "The Anglican: A Quarterly Gazette of the Anglican Society in North America", 1963-1979 (Box 75, Folder 770)
  - Miscellaneous, including "Metabagdad", 1963 (Box 75, Folder 771)
  - Scholarly: writings of friends/colleagues, 1957-1995, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 772-774)
- Biographical Documentation, 1958-1999; Series IX
  - Personal materials
    - Biographical sketches, no date (Box 76, Folder 775)
    - News items, 1975-1988 (Box 76, Folder 776)
    - Church Deployment Office profiles, 1970-1984 (Box 76, Folder 777)
    - Acknowledgments, 1957-1987 (Box 76, Folder 778)
    - Illustrations/drawings by HBP, no date (Box 76, Folder 779)
    - Honorary degree: Nashotah House, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 780)
    - Honorary degree: General Theological Seminary, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 781)
    - Honorary degree: Berkeley Divinity School, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 782)
    - HBP's memorabilia: round the world trip journal, 1960 (Box 76, Folder 783)